<resources>
    <string name="app_name">English for All</string>

    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_favourites">Favourites</string>
    <string name="less_16_01">How does television affect our lives? It can be very helpful and enjoyable to people who carefully select the programmes they watch. Through television is beneficial to people in many ways, it also has some ill effects on its <u>viewers</u>. Children are generally the most affected. It is time we awakened to its dangers.</string>
    <string name="less_16_02">There are, however, serious disadvantages with television. Long hours of watching can have an <u>adverse effect</u> on a person\'s phisical condition. Many people spend much of their free-time <u> slouched </u> in front of TV sets. As a result, they do not get enough physical exercise which is necessary for a healthy life. Further, watching television for long hours hinders the development of mind. It is well-known fact that the brain slows down when a person is watching television. Another disadvantage is that television often causes people to become dissatisfied with their lives. The reason for this, is that to many people, what they see in television: for instance, a tele - drama or an advertisement, become very real. People try to live something shown in the television and become depressed when they fail. Another danger in watching television is that some people cannot stop watching it and become addict to it. As a result they do not spend enough time on important areas of their lives, such as education, sports, reading, vising and entertaining with friends and family.</string>
<!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
